Guide to the Barnett Lipton papers, 1970-1993 MS2062
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- 2000 accretion, 1987-1993; MS2062 Series 2; 5 Linear feet
  - Official Stationery- Goodwill Games, Seattle WA, 07/1990-08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Goodwill Games, general articles, Seattle WA, 07/1990-08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Opening Ceremony-Goodwill Games, articles, Seattle WA, 07/1990-08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Closing Ceremonies-Goodwill Games, articles, Seattle WA, 07/1990-08/1990 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Complimentary Correspondence-Goodwill Games, Seattle WA, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Award of Excellence-Goodwill Games, Seattle WA, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Program-Operation Welcome Home, NYC, 06/09/1991 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Operation Welcome Home, articles, NYC, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Operation Welcome Home, photograph, NYC, 06/10/1991 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Complimentary Correspondence-Operation Welcome Home, NYC, 06/11/1991 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Stanford University's Centennial Celebration, articles, Stanford University, 09/1991 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Lipton-Self-Promotion, articles, undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Official Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Kimball International-Advertisement, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Proposals/Schedules/Itineraries for various events, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Tape, US Olympic Festival -Closing Ceremonies, Norman OK, 3/4in U-matic, 07/30/1989 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tape, US Olympic Festival-Opening Ceremonies, Norman OK, running time: 3:25min,VHS, 07/21/1989 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Tape, One to One Partnership: Mobilizing for the Next Generation, NYC, (production date), 3/4in U-matic, quad split, tape 1 of 2, 06/03/1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Tape, One to One Partnership: Mobilizing for the Next Generation, NYC, (production date), 3/4in U-matic, quad split, tape 2 of 2, 06/03/1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Tape, One to One Partnership: Mobilizing for the Next Generation-arrival of guests, NYC, (production date), 3/4in U-matic, tape 1 of 2, 06/09/1992 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Tape, One to One Partnership: Mobilizing for the Next Generation-arrival of guests, NYC, (production date), 3/4in U-matic, tape 2 of 2, 06/09/1992 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Tape, Making of the 1984 US Olympic Games-Olympic Challenge, Los Angeles CA, VHS, running time: 60min, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Tape, ITT Worldwide Management Conference-Highlights, Honolulu HI, VHS, running time: 2:35min, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Tape, Super Bowl XXV-Commercial Inserts, Tampa FL, 3/4in U-matic 01/18/1991, undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Tape, Polaroid 50th Anniversary Celebration, (production date), 3/4in U-matic, running time: 60min, 09/11/1987 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Tape, "Remembrance"-Tribute to Dr. Land-shown during Polaroid 50th anniversary Celebration, 3/4in U-matic, running time: 14:35min, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1990 Goodwill Games-Opening Ceremony, Norman OK, 3/4in U-matic, tape 1 of 2, 07/21/1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - 1990 Goodwill Games-Closing Ceremony and News Commentary, Norman OK, 3/4in U-matic, tape 2 of 2, 08/05/1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 1990 Goodwill Games-Opening Ceremony, Norman OK, running time: 3:45min, 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration, running time: 3:10min, 3/4in U-matic, 4/30/1989-07/21/1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - 200th Anniversary of George Washington's Inauguration-Local news coverage, NYC, 3/4in U-matic, 04/30/1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Tape, Operation Welcome Home Ticker Tape parade-Highlights, NYC, 3/4in U-matic, 06/10/1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Tape, "Larger than Life"-History of Czechoslovakian Spartakiada and full coverage of 1989 Spartakiada, Prague, (production date) 3/4in U-matic, tape 1 of 2 09/13/1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Tape, "Larger than Life"-History of Czechoslovakian Spartakiada and full coverage of 1989 Spartakiada, Prague, (production date), 3/4in U-matic, tape 2 of 2 09/13/1989, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular "The Making of", Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, tape 1 of 3 10/1/1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular "The Making of", Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, tape 2 of 3 10/1/1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular "The Making of", Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, tape 3 of 3 10/1/1991, undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular-video clips shown in celebration, Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, reel A 10/01/1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular- still frames shown in celebration, Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, reel B 10/01/1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular, Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, tape 1 of 3 10/01/1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular, Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, tape 2 of 3 10/01/1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tape, Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular, Stanford University, 3/4in U-matic, tape 3 of 3 10/01/1991, undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - professional color sketches for an unknown event, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - professional color sketches for an unknown event, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - professional color sketches for an unknown event, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - US Olympic Festival-Opening Ceremonies, Norman OK, 07/21/1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - US Olympic Festival-Opening Ceremonies, Norman OK, 07/21/1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - US Olympic Festival-Opening Ceremonies, Twin Cities MN, 07/06/1990 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - US Olympic Festival-Opening Ceremonies, Twin Cities MN, 07/06/1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - US Olympic Festival, Twin Cities, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Goodwill Games-Opening Ceremonies, Seattle WA, 07/21/1990 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Goodwill Games-Closing Ceremony, Seattle WA, 08/05/1990 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Operation Welcome Home, NYC, 06/10/1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Operation Welcome Home, NYC, 06/10/1991 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular, Stanford University, 10/01/1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Stanford University's Centennial Spectacular, Stanford University, 10/01/1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Unidentified Army/Navy Football Game, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)